homejobsforcitizens.org 2010-08-13

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

**Overview:**

**Home Jobs For Citizens** LLC ("Home Jobs For Citizens ", "Site," "we," "us," or "our") respects and are committed to protecting your privacy. That is why we have adopted this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is intended to explain our privacy practices and inform you as to: 

  * The kinds of personal information we collect from users of the Site and how that information is collected; 
  * How we use your personal information; 
  * The circumstances under which we disclose personal information to third parties; 
  * How you can access, update or delete any personal information collected about you by us; and 
  * The mechanisms we have implemented to protect your personal information.

We promise that we will take steps to use your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this Privacy Policy. The following policies are only regarding transactions made and data gathered on web pages, newsletters, discussion lists and opt-in announcement lists owned and operated by **Home Jobs For Citizens** and does not apply to any other transactions, information, web site or Internet, telephone or offline point of contact between **Home Jobs For Citizens** and you or other consumers.  As we continue to develop our Site and take advantage of technologies to improve the services we offer, this may change. Such revisions shall be effective to you immediately upon posting.  We therefore encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. 

This Site is offered and made available only to users 18 years of age or older who reside in the United States of America, its territories and possessions ("U.S"). If you are not yet 18 years old, or do not reside in the U.S., please discontinue using the Site immediately, or if, for any reason, you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not participate in the features, activities and services that require you to provide your personal information. This Privacy Policy is a part of the terms and conditions which are set forth in our Terms of Use Agreement. Both the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use Agreement are legally binding on all users. By using this web site, you consent to this Agreement and to the collection and use of information by **Home Jobs For Citizens** as specified below.   

**What information are you collecting and how are you collecting it?**   

Every computer connected to the Internet is given a domain name and a set of numbers that serve as that computer's "Internet Protocol" IP address. When a visitor requests a page from any Web site within the **Home Jobs For Citizens** Network, our Web servers automatically recognize that visitor's domain name and IP address. The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our site. We use this information to examine our traffic in aggregate, and to investigate misuse of the **Home Jobs For Citizens** Network, its users, or to cooperate with law enforcement. We do not collect and evaluate this information for specific individuals. Our Web servers do not record e-mail addresses of the visitors.   

**What are cookies?**   

From time to time, **Home Jobs For Citizens** or its advertisers may send a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other Web sites. Cookies do not damage your system. We use cookies to identify which areas of **Home Jobs For Citizens** ’ Network of Web sites you have visited or customized, so the next time you visit; those pages may be readily accessible. Our advertisers may also use cookies to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. **Home Jobs For Citizens** and/or our advertisers may use this information to better personalize the content, banners, and promotions that you see on our site. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our Site and other Web sites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended. 

** ** **What information do you collect when I register for something?**   

**Home Jobs For Citizens** offers access to some services that are free but that require registration. We may use your registration contact information to send notification of **Home Jobs For Citizens** products and services by e-mail and/or postal mail. We may also use your IP address internally and share it with third parties for reporting and statistical purposes.   

**What other information do you request?**   

We may also request your e-mail address or mailing address for the purposes of conducting a survey or to provide additional services (for example, subscriptions to e-mail newsletters, announcement lists or information about conferences and trade shows). Whenever we request the identity of a visitor, we will clearly indicate the purpose of the inquiry before the information is requested. 

We may from time to time send e-mail announcing new **Home Jobs For Citizens** products and services. Except as stated above, **Home Jobs For Citizens** will not send you e-mail that you have not agreed to receive. If you choose to supply your postal address in an online form, you may receive mailings from other third party companies. 

When you enter a contest or other promotion, we may ask for your name, address, and e-mail address so we can administer the contest and notify winners. 

**What information do you collect when I purchase something?**

If you are purchasing something from **Home Jobs For Citizens,** we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status. This information may also be used by us to notify you of related products and services. Credit card information will not be shared or sold to third parties for any purpose without your express permission. 

Wherever **Home Jobs For Citizens** collects personal information we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page. 

**Who do we share our information with?**

**Companies That Help Deliver Home Jobs For Citizens Products or Services**   
Sometimes we hire companies to help us deliver products or services (including processing your transaction, vendor direct shipping, credit card authorization and fraud prevention).  In those instances, we need to share your information with these companies. Sometimes we also work with other companies who assist us in gathering your information in order to enable us and the other businesses of **Home Jobs For Citizens** to provide you products and services. All of these companies are only allowed to use your information for delivery of the product or service. 

**Companies Offering Promotions, Products, or Services**

On occasion, **Home Jobs For Citizens** may share your information, unless you elect not to have us do so, with other unrelated outside third parties selected by us, so that these third parties can directly market their products or services via e-mail and/or postal mail. 

**_Information Sharing Between Affiliates_**

**Home Jobs For Citizens** reserves the right to share your personally identifiable information, including your email, postal address, phone number and purchase history, with its Affiliates. **Home Jobs For Citizens** may share your personally identifiable information with Affiliates in order to conduct promotions, offer special premiums, and share databases and equipment. We will not share your credit card information with anyone, including Affiliates, without your express permission. We reserve the right to share your information with other companies that become Affiliates. 

**Third-Party Advertisers**

Once you've clicked on a third-party advertisement and have left our Web site, our Privacy Policy no longer applies. You must read the privacy policy of the advertiser to see how your personal information will be handled on their site. 

**Purchase or Sale of Businesses**

As **Home Jobs For Citizens** continually strives to improve our business, from time to time, **Home Jobs For Citizens** may purchase a business or sell one or more of its businesses, and personally identifiable information regarding you may be transferred as a part of the purchase or sale.  If **Home Jobs For Citizens** purchases a business, the personally identifiable information received with that business would be treated in accordance with the privacy policy of that business on the date of sale. If **Home Jobs For Citizens** and/or its units or subsidiaries are ever sold, acquired, merged, liquidated, reorganized, or otherwise transferred, we reserve the right to transfer our user databases together with any personally identifiable information contained therein, to a third-party.  **Home Jobs For Citizens** will make reasonable efforts to include provisions in the selling contract to require the purchaser to treat your personally identifiable information in the same manner you requested under this Privacy Policy. 

**Content Partners**

On some of our sites, we provide content that is created by a third-party partner Web site. In some instances the third-party sites will collect information in order to facilitate the transaction or to make the use of their content more productive and efficient. In these circumstances the information collected is shared between **Home Jobs For Citizens** and our third-party sponsors.  These third parties will receive your information because you will be visiting their Web sites or using their links and, in doing so, you may provide information directly to them. You therefore should refer to their privacy policies to understand how they handle your information and what kinds of choices you have. 

On some of our sites, **Home Jobs For Citizens** may provide you with a link to the supplier of that product so that you may get further information. If you link to the supplier's site, the supplier may collect or receive information about you. 

You also may make a purchase from **Home Jobs For Citizens** through a link from another Web site or search engine and may use their express checkout tool to do so. When you do, please be aware that both **Home Jobs For Citizens** and that Web site or search engine will receive your information. 

**Mandatory Disclosures Required By Law**

**Home Jobs For Citizens** will disclose personal information and/or an IP address, when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: 

1) Conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on **Home Jobs For Citizens,**

2) Protect and defend the rights or property of the **Home Jobs For Citizens** Network of sites and related properties, or visitors to the **Home Jobs For Citizens** Network of sites and related properties, 

3) Identify persons who may be violating the law, the **Home Jobs For Citizens** Terms of Use Agreement, the rights of third parties, or otherwise misusing the **Home Jobs For Citizens** Network or its related properties, 

4) Cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities. 

**Your Control Over Your Personal Information**

**Opt-Out/Changing Your Status**

At any time, you can change choices you have previously made as to the use of your personal information. Every communication **Home Jobs For Citizens** sends you will contain a clearly worded "Opt-Out" or "Unsubscribe" link allowing you to withdraw your permission for future mailings. Alternatively, you can click this link to unsubscribe now http://www.reallistremoval.com/homejobsforcitizens.htm. This system is automated and must be contacted from the email address you wish to have removed. Permission changes will be honored as soon as possible after receipt. Please allow five to seven days for processing. Permission changes will however not affect any information which you provided to us and which we previously shared with our Content Partners.

**Editing Your Profile**

If you are a registered member, you have the ability to review and correct your personally identifiable information at any time. Simply sign into the site and click the "My Profile" link on the header of every page. There, you can change your address information, e-mail type, sign-in, and e-mail permissions.

**OTHER MATTERS**

**Your California Privacy Rights**

As of January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits visitors to this Site who are residents of California to request information regarding **Home Jobs For Citizens** ’ disclosure of their information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to our customer privacy care center at [support@HomeJobsForCitizens.org](mailto:support@GettingAmericaBackToWork.org). 

**Data Security**

**Home Jobs For Citizens** is committed to doing its best to maintain the security of information collected on our site. 

While no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure from intrusion, we have used and will continue to use commercially reasonable efforts to put in place the appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect.  When you place orders for purchased products or access your payment information, we use industry standard SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption technology to protect the storage and transfer of your data from unauthorized parties. Encryption is a process by which a message or information is scrambled while it is in transit to our website SSL codes the information transferred between you and the server, rendering it unreadable to anyone trying to intercept the information. In addition to our online security efforts, we take steps to protect your personal data offline, as well. All sensitive information and/or systems that house that information (i.e., computers or filing cabinet) have physically restricted access in our offices. Employees are granted access on a need-to-know basis pursuant to specific job function requirements (for example, a billing clerk or a customer service representative). Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices through periodic training sessions in an effort to keep security awareness levels high.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**

**Home Jobs For Citizens** will occasionally update this Privacy Policy in response to changing business circumstances and legal developments. If there are material changes to this Policy or in how **Home Jobs For Citizens** uses your personally identifiable information, **Home Jobs For Citizens** will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. **Home Jobs For Citizens** encourages you to periodically review this Policy to be informed of how we are protecting your information.   This Policy is current as of April 10, 2007. 

**Information About Children**

We are committed to protecting the privacy and rights of children online. We believe that children should be able to use the Internet in a safe, productive, and efficient manner and should be afforded the highest protection available with respect to their personal information. The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA") took effect on April 21, 2000 and imposes certain requirements on Web sites directed toward children under 13 that collect information on those children, or on Web sites that know they are collecting information on children under the age of 13. It currently is **Home Jobs For Citizens’** policy not to collect personal information on any person under 13. To learn more about COPPA, consult the Federal Trade Commission’s COPPA Web Site [www.ftc.gov](http://www.ftc.gov/) or you may call 202/FTC-HELP.

By using this web site, you consent to this Agreement and to the collection and use of information by **Home Jobs For Citizens** as specified above

**Contact Information**  
**Home Jobs For Citizens**  
351 W Washington  
Kearney, MO 64060
